canadagoose.com 2019-03-19

# Privacy Policy | Canada Goose | Canada Goose®

Effective Date: January 1, 2016

## Introduction

The following is the privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) of Canada Goose Inc. and its affiliates (“Canada Goose”, “we” or “us”). Canada Goose recognizes the importance of your right to privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your personal information.

## Categories of Information We Collect

“Personal Information” means any information about an identifiable individual by which you can be identified or contacted. The types of Personal Information we collect include: your name, mailing address, telephone or mobile number, birth date, payment card numbers, language preference, resume information, including your employment history and educational qualifications (if you submit employment applications), purchase/return/exchange information and e-mail address.

## Identifying Purposes for Collection of Personal Information

Canada Goose collects, uses and discloses Personal Information in order to provide you with goods and services and/or information on products and services you might be interested in. We also collect, use and disclose your Personal Information to comply with legal and regulatory requirements and as otherwise may be permitted or required by applicable laws. Canada Goose collects Personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * To identify and contact you when you request that products be sent to you or others, make purchases or returns with us, or place an order with us.
  * To fulfill orders, process payments and ship products purchased by you.
  * To establish and maintain commercial relations with you.
  * To provide you with ongoing service and product offers.
  * If you submit your resume in connection with an employment application, to review and consider the information that you submitted in connection with your possible employment by Canada Goose and otherwise in connection with the hiring process;
  * To respond to your inquiries.
  * To provide you with information about our products and warranty claims.
  * To support Canada Goose’s core business functions such as internal business processes, reporting, marketing and advertising.
  * To notify you of product recalls or safety issues.
  * To process and respond to your application for current or future career opportunities.
  * To meet legal and regulatory requirements.

Canada Goose’s Privacy Policy will apply to all Personal Information collected, used or disclosed by Canada Goose when an individual:

  * Makes an inquiry by telephone, by email or through our website.
  * Registers or provides information by email or through the internet.
  * Makes a purchase from Canada Goose’s Online Store.
  * Completes a customer profile or creates an account on the Online Store.
  * Applies for employment positions featured on our Site;
  * Issues a complaint regarding a Canada Goose product or service.
  * Makes a claim under Canada Goose’s warranty program.
  * Requests information or assistance from Canada Goose.
  * Participates or responds to consumer survey or requests for opinions, concerns, and preferences regarding Canada Goose’s products and services.
  * Participating in contests, sweepstakes and other promotions.
  * Using other features of the Canada Goose Web Site that may be offered from time to time.

## Limiting Collection of Personal Information

Canada Goose limits the collection of Personal Information to that which is necessary for the identified purposes in this Privacy Policy and will collect, use and disclose this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Personal Information will not be used without your consent for purposes other than those for which it was collected or in accordance with applicable laws. From time to time, we may wish to use your Personal Information for new or additional purposes. We will obtain your consent to use your Personal Information for such new or additional purposes before doing so. We may also use and disclose your Personal Information to other third parties under the following limited circumstances:

  * with service providers or suppliers that help with our business operations, our Web Site or Online Store, including those service providers and suppliers that help us market our products and services, provide analytics, process payments, administer programs, operations, fulfill requests, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, or product reviews; or
  * with your consent; or
  * when necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Canada Goose, our customers or employees, to detect and prevent fraud; or
  * when otherwise required or permitted by law.

From time to time, we may decide to sell or transfer all or part of our business to a related company or to a third party, to merge with another entity, to insure or securitize our assets, or to engage in another form of corporate or financing transaction (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale or other change in corporate control). In addition, the manner in which products, services, programs, contests, promotions and events are provided to you, and the organization providing those products, services, programs, contests, promotions or events, may also change. Where your Personal Information is required in connection with any such transactions, we may use and disclose such Personal Information and will require that the parties involved, including affiliates and advisors agree to protect your Personal Information with policies meeting standards equivalent to those set out in the Privacy Policy both during and after completion of the transaction. 

Additionally, any suppliers or service providers that have access to Personal Information are chosen carefully by us and are required to have privacy and security standards that meet our requirements. We uses contracts and other measures with our service providers and suppliers to maintain the confidentiality and security of users’ Personal Information and to prevent Personal Information from being used for any other purpose, including for any advertising or other commercial purposes. However, you should know that service providers and suppliers performing services on our behalf may store, transfer and process Personal Information on servers located outside of Canada, in jurisdictions (including the United States) whose data protection laws differ from those of Canada. As a result, Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. For example, information may be shared in response to valid demands or requests from government authorities, courts and law enforcement officials in those countries. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to require our service providers and suppliers to maintain protections on Personal Information that are equivalent to those that apply in Canada.

## Exceptions

This Privacy Policy does not impose any limits on the collection, use or disclosure of the following information by Canada Goose:

  * with information that is publicly available, such as a customer’s name, address and telephone number when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance;
  * name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization;
  * non-personal information, which is information that does not identify you; or
  * other information about a customer or an employee that is publicly available and is set out in Regulations made pursuant to the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (Canada).

## Placing an Order on the Canada Goose Online Store

If you place for a product with our Online Store, we request the information reasonably needed by us to complete the processing of your orders and billing. When we collect payment information directly from you, like credit card numbers and expiration dates, we transmit this data directly from you to the credit card processing company and it is not stored by Canada Goose. We also share our users' Personal Information with outside shipping companies and credit card processing companies in order to bill and ship your order, but we do not provide any more information than reasonably necessary for these purposes. We may also use the information to contact you regarding your order and to provide you with ongoing services and offers which may be of interest to you. 

## Cookies, Web Beacons, Tags and Other Similar Technologies

As you interact with our website, we may use automatic data collection technology and services to record and collect information that identifies your computer, tracks your use of our website and collects certain information about you and your surfing habits. This information may include information that identifies your device, IP address, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, keywords, date and time, what sections of a website you visit, and other similar information concerning your use. This information is used for fulfilling contracts with our business partners, and to help us serve you better by improving our website design, as well as our products, services, and promotions. 

Our website uses “cookie,” “web beacon,” “tag” and other similar technologies. A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer so that your computer will “remember” information when you visit a website. Web beacons and tags are small strings of code that are used in conjunction with a cookie and that allow us to record activity on our website. A web beacon allows us to capture certain additional types of information about a visitor's actions on a website, such as a visitor's cookie number, the time, date, duration and number of page views, a description of the page where the web beacon is placed, and details about any items that were purchased.

You can reject or disable cookies by managing your browser settings and following the directions provided in your Internet provider’s “help” file. If you turn off cookies, you may still visit the website, but you may not be able to use some areas of the website.

Information obtained through cookies, web beacons and tags may be shared with or obtained by service providers on our behalf. If third parties provide such analytics services and software (see the section immediately below), the third parties may also receive the information collected and their use of such information is governed by their privacy policies.

## Third-Party Advertising Partners

We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These advertising service providers may collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website, and your interactions with our products and services. Such non-identifiable information does not include your name, address, email address or other Personal Information. Such providers may place and access their own cookies, tags, web beacons or similar technologies on your computer or device used to access the website to serve you ads or other content personalized to your interests. In addition to the information about your visits to our website, our service providers may also use the information about your visits to other websites to target advertisements for products and services available from Canada Goose. 

As described above, you may be able to set your browser to refuse cookies. If you refuse cookies you may still receive online advertising, but it may be less personalized.

## “Do Not Track” Signals

Unless your browser settings are configured to make your online activities and publicly available information about your online activities (such as traffic data) invisible to usage analytics tools, we do not presently have the capability to omit you from usage analytics to the extent your browser only sends us a “do not track” signals or message and does not otherwise screen you from tracking without any action on our part. 

Third parties, other than our vendors (such as our website analytics provider), do not have authorization from us to track which websites you visited prior and after visiting our website. That said, we cannot control third party tracking and there may be some third party tracking over time and across third-party websites that occurs without our knowledge or consent.

## Third Party Links

Our website may contain links to other websites which are not under the control of Canada Goose. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each website to which we may link that may collect personal information.

## Information Received from Third Parties

We may receive information about you (including Personal Information) from third parties. For example, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from Canada Goose, that website will forward to us your email address and other information about you so that we may contact you as requested. You may also choose to participate in a third party application or feature (such as one of our pages on Facebook or another social platform or website) through which you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including Personal Information.

## Security

We maintain technical, physical and administrative security safeguards to protect your Personal Information against loss, theft, and unauthorized access. Any Personal Information you provide to us is exchanged on a secure server. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. 

## Accessing and Accuracy of your Personal Information

If you have registered for an account online, you may access certain categories of Personal Information by logging into your account. You may also request access to your Personal Information which we may hold by contacting our Canada Goose Privacy Officer at the contact information set forth below, and we will respond within the time periods provided for under applicable laws. We will need to verify your identity before providing you with the Personal Information we hold about you. There is no cost for such access request unless you require copies of records. We may not be able to provide you with access to your Personal Information if the information cannot be separated from the Personal Information of others, cannot be disclosed for reasons of security or commercial confidentiality, or is protected by legal privilege. If we cannot provide you with access to your Personal Information, we will advise you of the reasons access is being denied, unless we are prohibited by law from doing so.

You may request to update and change your Personal Information by e-mail or writing to the Canada Goose Privacy Officer at the contact information set forth below. We shall endeavor to correct or complete any Personal Information which you advise us is inaccurate or incomplete. If you have an account with our Online Store, you can log in and update your account information, including contact, billing and shipping information.

## E-mail Communications

Canada Goose complies with Canada’s anti-spam legislation (CASL) and we will not send you electronic communications in contravention of this law. Our Online Store allows you to sign up and expressly consent to receiving electronic communications. We will ensure that each e-mail includes an opt-out feature and instructions on how to un-subscribe if you no longer wish to receive future e-mails from us. You may also contact us at [ce@canadagoose.com](mailto:ce@CanadaGoose.com?Subject=Unsubscribe) to stop receiving them or can unsubscribe using the link included in the e-mail or by telephoning us at 1-888-276-6297. If you do not expressly consent to receiving electronic communications, we will only communicate with you during the time period and for the limited purposes permitted under CASL. 

If you do not wish to receive promotional mail, phone calls or emails, contact us at ce@canadagoose.com or 1-888-276-6297 to opt out. You also have the ability to unsubscribe to promotional e-mails via the opt-out link included in each promotional e-mail.

## Children’s Privacy

Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from such children through our website. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. If we learn that we have collected the Personal Information of such a child we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

## Notice to Residents Outside of Canada

Canada Goose is headquartered in Canada and our website is operated in Canada and the United States. Personal Information may be accessed by us or transferred to us in Canada or to our affiliates, business partners, or service providers elsewhere in the world. If you are located outside of Canada, please be advised that any information you provide to us will be transferred to and stored in Canada and that, by submitting information to us, you explicitly authorize its transfer and storage within Canada. We will protect the privacy and security of Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy regardless of where it is processed or stored. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code (known as the “Shine the Light Law”), residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, what types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information in the immediately preceding calendar year. To access this information, write to Canada Goose Inc., Care of: Privacy Officer, 250 Bowie Avenue, Toronto, ON M6E 2R9 or email [Privacyofficer@CanadaGoose.com](mailto:Privacyofficer@CanadaGoose.com?Subject=Privacy%20policy). 

Canada Goose will endeavor to respond to such requests within a reasonable time by providing a report that includes the information required by applicable law. Please be advised that Canada Goose is not required to respond to requests from any individual resident under the Shine the Light Law more frequently than once per calendar year.

## Consent

By submitting Personal Information to Canada Goose or its service providers and agents, you agree that Canada Goose may collect your Personal Information and you consent to the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by applicable law. 

Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you may refuse or withdraw your consent to certain of the purposes identified herein at any time by contacting Canada Goose at 1-888-668-0625. If you refuse or withdraw your consent, you acknowledge that Canada Goose may not be able to provide you or continue to provide you with certain services or information which may be of value to you. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Canada Goose reserves the right, in its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, without prior notice to you. Such changes, modifications, additions, or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting unless otherwise indicated. However, we will treat your continued use of our Canada Goose Web Site following such revision as your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to our privacy practices as described in the revised version of the Privacy Policy, please do not use the website in any manner, and we will continue to treat previously collected information in accordance with the privacy practices described in the applicable, prior version of this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## How to Contact Us - Canada Goose Privacy Officer

We welcome your feedback. To request a correction or to review your personal Personal Information, withdraw your consent to the use of your Personal Information, correct or update your Personal Information or wish to ask questions about privacy at Canada Goose, please contact Canada Goose’s Chief Privacy Officer at: [Privacyofficer@CanadaGoose.com](mailto:Privacyofficer@CanadaGoose.com?Subject=Privacy%20policy).
